[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long does it take for a sloth to digest its food completely?", "correct_answer": "A month or more", "incorrect_answers": ["1 week", "More than 2 weeks", "About 3 months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What two countries border the Netherlands?", "correct_answer": "Belgium and Germany", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany and Lithuania", "Germany and France", "France and Belgium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The worlds oldest lake is also the worlds deepest lake. Where would it be found?", "correct_answer": "Siberia", "incorrect_answers": ["Between Europe and Asia", "Israel", "Brazil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the capital city of Latvia?", "correct_answer": "Riga", "incorrect_answers": ["Reykjavik", "Port Vila", "Porto-Novo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What superhero does Hugh Jackman play in the X-Men series?", "correct_answer": "The Wolverine", "incorrect_answers": ["Professor Charles Xavier", "Iceman", "Colossus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vigo Mortensen plays a former gangster, who wants to escape his past and his brother in this thriller by David Cronenberg.", "correct_answer": "A History of Violence", "incorrect_answers": ["Dead Ringers", "Crimes of the Future", "Crash"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Isaac Newton formulate the famous equation E=mc\u00b2?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1971, this programmer implemented the first email system capable of sending mail between users on different hosts connected to the ARPANET.", "correct_answer": "Ray Tomlinson", "incorrect_answers": ["David Thomson", "John Tomlinson", "Mark Thomson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To which of these geographical areas are hummingbirds indigenous?", "correct_answer": "North and South America", "incorrect_answers": ["Europe", "Africa and Asia", "Australia and Tasmania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of this chemical compound, coined by German-Swiss chemist Christian Friedrich Sch\u00f6nbein in 1840, comes from the Greek word for smell.", "correct_answer": "Ozone", "incorrect_answers": ["Silicone", "Osmium", "Aroclor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fact that stretching prevents injuries is a myth.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following movies released in 1996, boasts the use of 50 gallons of blood?", "correct_answer": "Scream", "incorrect_answers": ["April Fools Day", "I Know What You Did Last Summer", "Seven"]}]